A sound soul, dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
The guard's fast asleep. Perfect.
Who's there? Talk to me.
I... I was sent here by someone who wants to break you out of that cell and free you from witch prison.
I'm gonna let you out now, okay?
What kind of person do you think I am? You think I take handouts from whoever comes along?
Thank you!
No problem.
It's easy to get out of there when you got someone on the outside with a key.
But you wanna know what I was gonna try before you showed up? I had a plan.
Never mind that. We need to hurry. They'll be coming after us.
See, I was planning to try that thing they do in the movies.
You know where they tunnel under the wall by using a spoon to steadily dig away at the ground underneath it?
I always thought that was a really cool idea when they did that. So, I decided I would give it a try myself.
But all they ever gave me was chopsticks!
You can't dig with those!
I tried to think of another way out. I thought about it all the time.
And I realized something. I'm just not an idea man.
I suppose it doesn't matter now, but you could have peed on the bars of your cell every day and gradually corroded them away, right?
Oh, damn it! Why did I try that? I'm such an idiot!
We have to hurry! They're coming after us!
If your hands and feet are still shackled like that, you can't fight and we'll...
Be careful. I smell someone nearby.
They're already here!
Listen up, Prisoner 13, man with the magic eye! If you resist, we'll show you no mercy!
I was locked inside that prison for 200 years.
If you think I'm gonna let you take me back there without putting up a fight, then you're all crazy!
Oh no! This is really bad!
If I don't get you out of here, then I'm gonna end up dead too!
Calm down. It'll take more than that to kill me. You should know that.
Damn! Don't!
You think the Grand Witch kept me alive all this time just for fun? She couldn't kill me.
See, that would have been tough considering.
I'm immortal.
I'll see you next time.
Do you want to back down now?
It's not too late.
No, we'll still do it.
Hey!
Your Meister has made a decision.
Now accept it.
Why are you so anxious to do this, Maka?
Fine, let's begin then.
Turn around so that you're facing each other.
Now tell your partner what his or her flaws are.
Our special lesson is insulting each other?
Yes, you could say that.
You're stubborn and reckless.
All you like to do for fun is read so you're boring and you have fat ankles.
That's another one.
You always hit me.
That's a flaw, right?
Professor, is beating me up part of the lesson?
No more beating on soul, Maka.
Oh, hey, I thought...
This may seem like a meaningless training exercise to them, but these are no ordinary candles.
They're designed to heighten a person's emotions.
With these burning, even a casual remark could ruin their friendship.
But if they can get beyond this, they will be better for it.
Their soul wavelengths will resonate even more strongly than before.
What's going on?
You've been acting weird lately.
You never even asked if I wanted to do this lesson.
I want to know what this is really about.
This is about me getting stronger so I can keep you from getting hurt that badly ever again.
The Meister fights in order to make the weapon stronger.
You know that.
You want to get stronger in order to protect your weapon.
That's all backwards.
You're crazy.
Crazy?
And why shouldn't I want to be stronger?
I hate having to be protected by you, soul.
Don't yell so loud.
It's annoying me.
I'll shout if I want to.
You're the one who's crazy, soul.
Why are you so against me getting stronger?
You're going to need more power.
Power so overwhelmingly strong you can say goodbye to all your fears.
Find a room to break.
It will make you stronger than you thought possible.
I'm not afraid of that little demon.
I'm not afraid of becoming stronger either.
Forget about it and sit down, will you?
You're hurting my neck.
I won't.
This isn't good.
Their soul wavelengths are beginning to slip.
The man with the magic eye.
Soul and Maka's diverging soul wavelength?
You did it?
Uh-huh.
I brought the guy.
Good work, Erika.
I've done my part.
Now take all your snakes out of my body like you promised you would.
Oh.
Oh, no.
You must be joking.
I'll remove one snake for every errand you run.
Huh?
How many more of them are there?
That's not something you need to know right now.
Of course, I could bring them all out at once.
You'd be ripped apart in the process, though.
Ah!
That's awful!
How could you, devil woman?
You're the one who set me free?
I wouldn't have expected it from a witch.
Yes, I'm Medusa.
Nice to meet you, man with the magic eye.
Man with the magic eye, huh?
Of course.
What else could you call me, after all?
In that prison, even my name was taken away from me.
But as of today, I'm officially free again.
All right, then.
My new name is Free.
Yes, that's right.
You're free.
Free, huh?
We'll have to see about that, won't we?
I owe you one.
I'd like to repay you somehow.
No, no.
That's all right.
Don't worry about it.
Please let me.
I'd like to settle my debts.
Well, maybe there is one thing I could ask you to do for me.
There's a certain weapon in Meister Pair I would like to see crushed.
From the DWMA.
That what you mean?
Yes.
I don't like death or that school of his, with all his damn rules.
You've got a deal, witch.
I'll take him out.
Hello, London!
Black Star has arrived!
Yahoo!
It's snowing.
Aren't you freezing?
Who cares about snow?
Snow can't touch me.
I could be naked out here and it wouldn't bother me at all.
This whole thing sucks.
Ever since Sol got himself hurt by that demon sword, all our extra lessons have to be done
with at least two teams.
You guys better not slow me down, okay?
Hey, you two, would you come take a look at this?
It's so beautiful at night, don't you think?
Yay, London!
What's with them?
Anyway, Maka, I can't detect souls, so this one's up to you.
Tell us what you see.
I'm on it.
Okay, let's see.
I'm focusing in on any souls that are in this area.
There's one right there.
Hey, you're right.
What does that do?
I don't know.
Something's wrong with his soul.
It's not normal.
There's a bunch of stuff all mixed together.
Some human, some witch.
And I'm sensing something else, too.
Here you are.
This guy wants a fight.
Looks like our lesson is getting off to a good start.
Be careful, though.
He's probably able to use magic.
Tsubaki, enchanted sword mode.
Let's finish this guy off quickly.
But you still can't handle that one.
I just have to last for a few seconds.
Let's go.
Yeah, right.
Impressive.
He's strong.
Let's go, soul resonance.
Amazing.
The resonance is still stable.
And is that Blackstar's soul?
London Bridge is falling down, dude.
Wolf, wolves, wolf, wolves.
Ice cone!
Tsubaki, right!
What?
She stopped it with her shadow.
How about a taste of my new technique?
Shadow star!
Star!
I told you it was too much for you.
He didn't even last ten seconds.
Blackstar might be strong, all right.
But he's still crazy.
Now then, who's next?
You shouldn't drop your guard like that, mister.
He got him.
No.
Soul, get out of there!
It happens a lot.
But fortunately, I can afford to let my guard down.
What's with this guy?
What's he doing?
Look at that!
His wound's closing up!
Of course it's closing up.
What else would it do?
I am immortal!
This guy, is it immortal?
Maybe it would help if you could see my true form.
What do you mean, your true form?
What's happening to the shape of his soul?
It's changing!
Ah!
You know who he is now.
You've run into the legendary Wolfman.
The one who stole the witch's eye!
Ah!
What?
It's like before.
That time when Blackstar and Soul were fighting kids.
Blackstar tried to lift Soul, but couldn't.
And this time, Soul's handle burned Maka.
I don't think their Soul wavelengths are in sync.
Poor Soul Eater, with all that black blood still inside of you.
How are you and your precious Maestro Maka going to handle this turn of events, I wonder?
And so, the experiment begins.
So difficult to breathe.
Why is this happening?
How do I breathe again?
Just inhale and exhale, right?
And how do I use my weapon?
Fighting won't miss.
Let's go!
Maka!
I'm Zillinger!
Soul!
Magic Eye Cannon!
Dammit, that was not good.
I always forget not to put those things where they can skewer me.
But it's okay.
No problem at all.
Nothing to see here.
After all, I'm immortal.
He's an immortal magic werewolf.
I can't deny that this guy is strong, but he sure is clumsy.
I guess sitting in a witch prison for 200 years would make anyone rusty.
I can't seem to handle my magic as well as I used to.
Maka!
We have to do something!
If you can't use Soul, try fighting with me!
It won't work.
Even if I could figure out how to use you in time, I still wouldn't be able to defeat him.
You Meisters.
The Great Lord Death plays by his own rules.
It's those rules that decide what evil is.
What are you talking about?
You all follow the Reaper so blindly.
What gives him the right to decide how the world should be run?
He trains you to hunt down souls he believes are unworthy, and a soul like mine wouldn't be safe from him.
But I for one am not going to accept that kind of future.
I refuse!
It's my turn now.
I'm gonna be the judge!
I'm not gonna play by his rules anymore!
Maka!
Soul, transform back into a scythe.
Wait, Maka.
You couldn't even hold me before.
Do it!
Using a weapon when your wavelengths aren't in sync is incredibly hard on the mind as well as the body.
But what else can she do?
Maka is a scythe-meister and Soul is her weapon.
Maka, your hands!
I'm going to become...
stronger!
Take that!
You'll have to do better than that.
How fast!
Damn!
What are you doing?
Calm down!
Take a breath!
Stay out of it!
I'm going to do this!
I refuse to let him defeat me!
Don't be an idiot!
If Shadow like a spoiled brat made you stronger, everyone would do it!
Shut up!
It's because of you saying stuff like that that our wavelengths are out of sync!
That's not cool, Soul!
It isn't cool at all!
Gain power!
I can show you how if you need!
Shut your mouth, Maka!
What do you even know anyway?
That was enough, you two!
You guys are a team!
You have to work together if you want to do anything!
One person can't make a decision without the other!
You decide together and you fight together!
Right!
Like Blackstar stopped to consult you every time he's about to do something stupid!
I'll admit Blackstar makes some dumb calls from time to time,
but the important thing is I'm here to back him up no matter how big a fool he is!
If we're fools, we're fools together! That's the kind of team we are!
Maybe Tsubaki's right.
I want to become stronger, but there's no reason I have to do it alone.
All I've been thinking about this whole time was catching up to Soul somehow.
No matter how hot it gets, I'm not letting go.
Soul and I are going to grow stronger together!
I don't get what you've been so worried about. I'm not even all that strong.
If you're done telling me what to do, maybe we can work together now.
Hey, demon guy.
You can lead me wherever you want.
Let's hear your plan, and we'll see whether I follow him.
In that case, come with me. Overwhelming madness and power await.
You got it.
Let's go! Soul Resonance!
Excellent.
Finally, the Black Blood is starting to do its work.
Wow! Their Soul Resonance rate is incredible!
What's happening? Something's wrong.
Is Soul devouring me?
This should be interesting. A weapon with Black Blood has the power to swallow its Meister's mind.
Now, let's see you raise your Resonance rate even higher.
Damn! It feels like my consciousness is being carried away!
No!
I won't let it. I will stay in control!
The legendary super skill of the Scythe Meister!
Witch Meister!
Fenty Tecnic, mindpying me.
Mine might be.
Woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof-woof.
We can get past that!
Ha-aaaah!
Ah!
It doesn't hurt. It's not hot. I'm not scared. I will not be beaten.
I won't ever let Sol get hurt again.
I'm going to get stronger!
Figure six, Hunter!
What the hell?!
We get him?
Almost there.
A Meister throwing her weapon aside and attacking!
Maka!
Down you go!
Soul!
I guess your ankles aren't that fat.
Maka!
If you think I'm falling all by myself, think again.
I'm taking you with me!
Maka!
Damn!
There's no way I'm letting you go!
Yahoo!
It's a good thing I'm here to look out for you two!
This isn't over yet!
Wolf wolves, wolf wolves, wolf wolves!
I'll just make a nice cylinder under my feet, kick off it and fly back up there!
I can do that, right?
Of course I can!
I'm immortal, I can do whatever I want!
I'm cylinder!
Wrong place again!
A truly impressive screw up, even for him.
My first fight in 200 years, and I screwed it up.
I'll get it right next time.
I just need some practice.
Yeah, just a little bit.
I've seen enough to convince me.
If I continue my research on black blood, I am certain I can create a Kishin.
Are you sure you're gonna be all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Thanks.
From the way your hands look, I'm guessing I'll be the one on cooking duty for a while, huh?
Heh, that oughta be interesting.
Black blood?
Blood?
Kuzu-boshi, kira-me-ku, yume-no, hoshi-sa, I wanna be, y'kou-ze, y'kou-ze, y'kou-ze!
I wanna be, y'kou-ze, y'kou-ze, y'kou-ze!
Thank you.
I love karaoke, too. I feel a star moment coming on.
So, should we eat fish and chips or fish and chips?
Food, karaoke, then sightseeing!
If we're feeling crazy, we could try some bangers and mash.
I'm kind of tired. Maybe I'll just go home and watch TV.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the super-written exam.
Heart-bounding, reeling, and restless? You're kidding.
What? We have a test next week?
Oh, man, that spoiled my appetite.
No Yorkshire pudding for me.